His Real Life Was The Biggest Fantasy Of All.
My Dinner with Hervé is a drama, tv movie film directed by Sacha Gervasi.
An unlikely friendship evolves over one wild night in LA between a struggling journalist and actor Hervé
Villechaize, the world's most famous gun-toting dwarf, resulting in life-changing consequences for both.
Danny Tate, played by Jamie Dornan.
Hervé Villechaize, played by Peter Dinklage.
Kathy Self, played by Mireille Enos.
Katie, played by Oona Chaplin.
Baskin, played by Harriet Walter.
Koski, played by Jim Sturgeon.
My Dinner with Hervé is an American television drama film written and directed by Sacha Gervasi, based on the
later days of actor Hervé Villechaize, its title a riff on Louis Malle's My Dinner with Andre.
The film stars Peter Dinklage as Villechaize, Jamie Dornan as a struggling journalist,
and Andy García as Villechaize's Fantasy Island co-star Ricardo Montalbán.
It premiered on HBO on October 20, 2018, and received generally positive reviews
from critics, who praised the performances of Dinklage and Dornan.
The tone is emotional.